我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
收到信息
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
presisco
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
还要多久我们才能使用钻头?
How much longer till we can use the drill?
其实,有了我们从月球基地得到的新的坐标,
Well, with the new coordinates we got from the moonbase,
我们应该可以行动了
we should be ready to go.
但我们真的该先进行一些测试
But we really should perform a few tests first.
哦!
Oh!
史蒂文
Steven.
橄榄石
Peridot.
我得跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
呃,好啊,没问题
Uh, yeah. Sure.
为什么我们要在这个坏掉的载具里?
Why are we in this broken-down vehicle?
我想问你一下...
I wanted to ask you...
关于钻石吗?
About the diamonds?
噢!
Oh!
我不知道其他人是怎么跟你说的,
I don't know what the others have told you,
但钻石掌权时有原因的
but there's a reason they're in charge.
为什么?
Why's that?
她们客观上来讲要比我们更优秀
They're objectively better than us.
每个宝石人都有自己的优势与弱点-
Every gem has their strengths and weaknesses --
但她们不是
but not them.
她们是绝对,完全,肯定无瑕的存在!
They're absolutely, totally, completely flawless beings!
尤其是我的钻石-黄钻石
Especially my diamond -- yellow diamond.
最完美,最理性,理智,
The most perfect, the most reasonable, rational,
完美的决策者-放到全宇宙也是
efficient decider ever to exist in the Universe.
你对她真是忠诚啊,不是吗?
You're really loyal to her, aren't you?
我怎么可能不呢?
How could I not be?
我们间也许有小小的休战协议,
We might have our little truce,
但我永远不会背叛我服务的宝石人的
but I'll never forsake the gem I was made for.
那很好,因为她就在你背后
That's good, because she's right behind you.
啊?
What?
啊啊,不!
Aah, no!
别挣扎了!
Save your strength!
你面对的是地球
You're up against one of the earth's
最伟大的囚禁技术之一-
greatest trapping technologies --
儿童安全锁!
the child safety lock!
不!不!
No! No!
你怎么能这样对我-伟大而可爱的橄榄石?!
How could you do this to me -- the great and lovable Peridot?!
我以为我们总算是朋友了,就像你希望的那样!
I thought we were finally friends, like you wanted!
我看到你将这个偷偷带出了月球基地
I saw you sneak this off the moon base
就在没人注意的时候!
while no one else was looking!
这是什么?从实招来!
What is it? Tell me!
这没什么特别的...
It's nothing special...
而且绝对不重要!
And definitely not important at all!
嗯...
Hmm.
那我为什么不砸了它呢?!
Then why don't I just smash it?!
不不不不,等等!
No, no, no, no, wait!
好吧,听着
All right, look.
我有个计划,容许我解释一下
I have a plan. Allow me to explain.
这是个...通讯器
It's... A communicator.
用来快速的
Meant for the express purpose
与母世界的钻石通讯
of contacting the diamonds back on homeworld.
你仍然在试图与母世界联系?
You're still trying to contact homeworld?
对,当然!我想通了!
Yes. Of course! I figured it out!
你们这群幼稚的草包总是试图保护地球,
You simple clods keep trying to protect the earth,
但你们什么事都做不对!
but you can't do anything right!
我自己都被带偏了-
I let myself get carried away, too --
欢笑,歌唱,建造我们的小小机器!
laughing, singing, building our little machine!
但你看不出来吗?这都没有用!
But don't you see? None of that matters!
真正重要的是我对黄钻石有所贡献!
All that matters is that I'm of use to yellow diamond!
这个星球可以对黄钻石有所贡献!
This planet can be of use to yellow diamond!
我必须要联系她-向她说明我所发现的情况!
I must contact her -- to reveal what I've discovered!
但是钻石都很坏啊!
But the diamonds are bad!
她们并不在乎地球
They don't care about the earth.
她们之前想将它掏空,
They wanted to hollow it out,
而现在她们又要用融合簇将地球炸毁!
and now they want to blow it up with the cluster!
对,对!
Yes, yes!
就是这个!
That's the point!
呃!
Ugh!
为何我总是不顾反对的支持你!
Why do I keep sticking my neck out for you!
你永远也不会站到我们这边!
You're never gonna be on our side!
石榴,紫晶,珍珠!
Garnet, Amethyst, Pearl!
史蒂文,别-别叫她们!
Steven, no -- don't get them!
史蒂文!
Steven!
放我走吧!
Release me!
她从月球基地拿了一个
She took a direct line to the diamonds
与钻石的直连通讯器?
from the moon base?!
她在想什么啊?
What was she thinking?!
天哪,就算我们一起经历了这么多,
Man, after everything we've gone through,
她仍然想搞事情
she's still out to get us.
哦,我要收回我给她起的所有炫酷外号
Oh, I'm taking back all my cool nicknames for her.
再见了,"橄榄"和"橄石"
So long "Perry" and "p-dot."
你好,"橄"...
Hello, p...
啊啊!我太生气了!
Aah! I'm too mad!
我以后再想想吧!
I'll think of something later!
我看她现在搞清楚什么是喇叭了
I see she knows what a horn is now.
史蒂文的动作与装束与《南方公园》的肯尼相同
你给她了许多的信任
You offered her a lot of your trust.
当然!
I did!
结果却糊了我一脸
And it blew up in my face.
你们已经保护地球
You guys have been protecting the earth
几千年了!
for thousands of years!
她本可能	[破坏掉这一切-
She could have destroyed all of that --
一整个地球!
a whole earth!
为什么我以为我能改变她的的想法?
Why did I think I could change her mind?
呃,我知道,对吧?
Ugh. I know, right?
但我想你不能,像是,进入别人的头脑
But I guess you can't, like, get into other people's heads
然后改变她们的想法
and change what they think.
哦,也许我们可以?
Oh, maybe we can?
对啊!
Yeah!
如果我们缩得非常小,
If we just shrink down really little,
我们就能进入-不不不!
we can get in -- no, no, no!
我不想命令她做该做的事
I don't want to tell her what to do.
她应该要理解,不是吗?
She should just know, shouldn't she?
你相信任何人都能洗,这很好,史蒂文
It's good you believe in everyone, Steven.
就像你母亲,
Like your mother,
相比我们你似乎有多一点的耐心
you seem to have a little more patience than the rest of us.
但事实是不是所有人配得上这种耐心
But the truth is not everyone deserves that patience.
往好处想-
Look on the bright side --
至少你把这个从她手里拿走了
at least you got this thing away from her
避免了她可能制造的破坏
before she did any real damage.
对啊
Yeah.
哦,不!
Oh, no!
自由!自由!
Free, free!
她怎么逃脱的?
How did she escape?!
噢!笨蛋!
Oh! Fools!
你的不可见旋转护盾可阻挡不了我-
Your invisible rotary shield was no match for me --
只要我使用逻辑的话!
once I applied logic!
现在我要正确的完成这一切!
Now I'm gonna do this right!
呃!看到了吗?
Ugh! See?
你们没人知道自己在做什么!
None of you know what you're doing!
哦,吼吼吼!
Oh-ho ho-kay!
我早就准备好了!
I've been ready for this!
快上车!
Get in.
史蒂文呢?
Where's Steven?
垃圾橄榄石!
Stupid Peridot!
垃圾巨型机器人!
Stupid giant robot!
哦,为何,哦,为何我非得鼓励她?
Oh, why, oh, why did I have to encourage her?
没时间难受了
There's no time for feeling horrible.
我们得在橄榄石与黄钻石取得联系前抓住她!
We have to catch Peridot before she contacts yellow diamond!
没错
That's right.
你尽可在回到神庙后难受个够
You can feel horrible all you want back at the temple.
怎么样,鼻涕石?
What's up, peri-snot?
说得好,紫晶!
Good one, Amethyst!
猛犬扑堆!
Dog pile!
不,不!
No, no!
你可别想逃走!
You're not getting away with it!
我信任过你!
I trusted you!
我花了那么多时间和你交流,心怀期待,
I spent all that time bonding and hoping
关怀备至!
and caring about you!
你也没想清楚!
You don't get it, either!
这就是你的...
This is your whole...
问题!
...problem!
你的感性驱散了理性!
Your emotions rule out reason!
我会完成该完成的工作!
I will do what has to be done!
哈?
Huh?
她会解决这个的
She'll sort this out.
这里是黄钻石控制室
This is the yellow diamond control room.
那是又一个珍珠吗?
Is that another Pearl?
她是谁?
Who is she?
不是所有珍珠都认识彼此的,史蒂文
Not all pearls know each other, Steven.
是谁授权你进行此次通话的?
Who authorized you to make this call?
没有人
No one.
但-但这是紧急情况!
B-but it's an emergency!
这不是使用
That's no excuse to use
钻石直连通信通道的借口!
the direct diamond communication channel!
珍珠?
Pearl?
是的,我的钻石?
Yes, my diamond?
为什么有人在钻石专线上?
Why is there someone on the diamond line?
我不清楚!
I don't know!
我刚准备告诉她-
I was just about to tell her that --
我来接管吧
I'll take it from here.
那是...
Is that...
黄...钻石
Yellow... Diamond.
我的钻石!橄榄石来此报告!
My diamond! Peridot reporting in!
哪个橄榄石?
Which Peridot?
切-切面2f5l,切割5xg
F-facet 2f5l, cut 5xg.
我很抱歉用这种方法与您联系
I'm sorry to contact you this way,
但所有其他的通讯手段
but all other forms of communication
都被破坏了,而且-
have been destroyed and --
看来你的任务进度滞后了...
this says you're behind schedule on your mission to...
地球怎么样了?
How is the earth?
那里充满了生命!
It's full of life!
有机生命
Organic life.
那么我分配给你的铁石英呢?
And where is the Jasper I assigned you?
还有为什么你不从飞船上通话呢?
And why aren't you calling from the ship?
哦,嗯...
Oh, hmm...
飞船被摧毁了
The ship was destroyed.
被谁?
By whom?
它-它-它是被...
It -- it -- it was destroyed by...
没人干的!
No one!
发生了一场意外...
There was an accident...
就在我们着陆时
While we were landing.
我会告知你上司你的无能的
I'll inform your manager of your incompetence.
还有,融合簇的状态呢?
And what is the status of the cluster?
融合簇会很快孵化的!
The cluster will emerge shortly!
好
Good.
我们总算能从那可悲的星球榨取出一点点成果了
We'll finally get some use out of that miserable planet.
谢谢你的报告,橄榄石
Thank you for your report, Peridot.
会有一艘飞船前往你的位置
There'll be a ship heading to your location
带你前往下一项任务
to take you to your next assignment.
等下!
Wait!
我-我不会为了用
I -- I wouldn't have called
报告浪费您的时间而进行通话的!
just to waste your time with a report!
你已经是了
You already have.
不,我是指,我进行通话的原因,
No, I mean, the reason I've called,
真正的原因是...
the real reason is...
我相信我们应该终止融合簇!
I believe we should terminate the cluster!
为什么?
Why?
这个世界的有机生态系统创造了独有的资源
The organic ecosystem creates resources unique to this world.
我们不能牺牲掉所有的可能性
We can't sacrifice all that potential
就为了一个超级武器!
just for one geo-weapon!
我想告诉您一些我想到的方案
I'd like to tell you some plans I came up with
用来利用这个星球而不干扰当地的-
to utilize the planet without disrupting the local --
我听够了
I've heard enough.
我不在乎潜力和资源
I don't care about potential and resources.
蛤?
What?
我想要我的融合簇,
I want my cluster,
而且我想让那个星球死掉
and I want that planet to die.
只需要让那发生
Just make that happen.
不!
No!
啊?!
Huh?!
你是在质疑我的权威吗?
Are you questioning my authority?
我只是在怀疑您的客观性,我的钻石
I'm questioning your objectivity, my diamond.
牛啊!
Well!
你真是胆大啊!
You are out of line.
我只是认为-
I just think --
我不在乎
I'm not interested
一个橄榄石的卑微的想法
in the puny thoughts of a Peridot.
但-
But --
你的出现已经冒犯了这个频道与我的时间,
you have disrespected this channel and my time with your presence,
而你应该
and you would do well to
但是
but
闭上嘴!
shut your mouth!
你在这个任务的每个阶段都失败了
You have failed at every stage of this mission.
你救赎自己的唯一机会
Your only chance to redeem yourself
就是遵守这个简单的命令-
is to obey this simple order --
你要让融合簇继续生长!
you are to leave the cluster to grow!
它会拆碎地球,
It will tear apart the earth,
而我也会感受到巨大的满足
and I will take immense satisfaction
将那个丑恶的石头
in erasing that hideous rock
从我的星图上抹去!
off of our star maps!
清楚吗?!
Is that clear?!
我不会做的!
I won't do it!
我可以肯定的告诉你
I can tell you with certainty
这个星球上有很多值得保护的东西!
that there are things on this planet worth protecting!
你对地球又了解什么 ?!
What do you know about the earth?!
显然比你要多,你个草包!
Apparently more than you, you clod!
呃,橄榄石,结束!
Uh, Peridot, out!
那真是太棒了!
That was amazing!
我不敢相信我刚才做了那个
I can't believe I just did that.
我之前真错误的理解你真错误的对待我了!
I was so wrong about being so wrong about you!
我不敢相信我刚才做了那个
I can't believe I just did that.
你认为你能改变她的想法
You thought you could change her mind.
黄B被橄榄屌干了个底朝天!
Yellow d got torn down by the peridactyl!
呃～
Ugh!
你们有人能拿这个嘛?
Can one of you take this?
为什么?
Why?
因为它可以被遥控引爆
Because it can be remotely detonated.
我们该怎么阻止它?
How do we stop it?
赶紧丢掉它吧!
Just get rid of it!
呃,给你,紫晶!
Uh, here, Amethyst!
我又该拿它怎么办?!
What am I supposed to do with it?!
我以为我能跟她讲道理
I thought I could reason with her.
没错,你真的把她气疯了
Yeah, you really made her mad.
然后你当面顶撞了她
And then you insulted her to her face.
你知道这意味着什么吗?
Do you know what this means?
我是我家乡的叛徒
I'm a traitor to my homeworld.
你是个水晶战士了!
You're a Crystal Gem!
不论你愿不愿意!
Whether you like it or not.
哦～
Oh!